welcome everyone to one of the final
欢迎大家参加决赛之一
sessions of spring one house everyone
春季大家一堂
had their time during the conference was
在会议期间有时间
okay all right so this afternoon we have
好吧，所以今天下午我们有
the keynote and this is probably one of
主题演讲，这可能是其中之一
the last sessions so I hope I'm not
最后几节课，所以我希望我不会
gonna be too boring so everyone stays
会很无聊，所以每个人都留下来
awake and goes home with a great feeling
醒着，心情舒畅
so I'm gonna be talking about how to
所以我要说的是
write your own spring boots starter and
编写自己的弹簧靴启动器，
how the spring boot starter how they
春季启动启动器如何
actually work in the spring boots
实际上在 spring boot 上工作
ecosystem and my name is Deidre bow by
生态系统，我叫Deidre bow
the way
方式
you can see my Twitter handle there if
你可以在那里看到我的Twitter句柄
you want to see some goofy stuff during
你想看一些愚蠢的东西
the week and some geeky stuff so a
这个星期和一些令人讨厌的东西，所以
little bit about a little bit about me I
关于我的一点点我
won't keep it too long that's my name
不会保留太久，这就是我的名字
I'm a Java consultant in Belgium at
我是比利时的Java顾问
ordina I work in the Jay Burks units we
我在杰伊·伯克斯（Jay Burks）的单位工作
basically do Java and JavaScript
基本上做Java和JavaScript
consultancy we have about a hundred
咨询我们大约有一百个
people
人
I'm the cloud and pass competence leads
我是云，并通过能力领导
or we organize workshops for our
或者我们为我们组织研讨会
colleagues and for external people about
同事和外部人
anything related to pass and cloud so
任何与通行证和云有关的东西
Cloud Foundry kubernetes all these kind
所有类型的Cloud Foundry kubernetes
of stuff and the different offerings we
的东西和我们提供的不同产品
we take care of that I've been a spring
我们照顾到我已经是春天了
lover since I've been developing in Java
自从我一直从事Java开发以来
for about 10 years now so I wasn't at
大约十年了，所以我不在
the very beginning of spring but I've
春天的开始，但我已经
seen a lot of evolutions going on I like
看到了很多不断发展的过程，我喜欢
the game I blog a bit I code in my free
我写博客的游戏我免费编写代码
time just side projects and I'm an avid
我只是一个侧面项目而已
soccer player so if anyone enjoy soccer
足球运动员，所以如果有人喜欢足球
yeah we say football but yeah so
是的，我们说足球，是的，所以
everyone answers understands this is my
每个人的答案都知道这是我的
very informal big picture they told us
他们告诉我们非常非正式的大图景
to take an informal picture so I took
拍一张非正式的照片，所以我拍了
one and and then I saw when I was
一个，然后我看到我何时
selected that all the rest had really
选择其余所有的
formal pictures so I'm probably the only
正式的照片，所以我可能是唯一的
one with alcohol on my hands in my
一个用酒精在我的手上
picture so I don't want to show the rest
图片，所以我不想显示其余的
of the picture because it's it's
图片的原因是因为
you already see enough so spring boots
你已经看到足够了，所以 spring boot
I'm not gonna be talking too long about
我不会谈论太久
spring boots since it's very well known
spring boot ，因为它是众所周知的
already I think but basically what it
我已经想过，但基本上是什么
does is it provides an open Yeti
是不是它提供了一个开放的雪人
opinionated view of building
固执的建筑观
production-ready spring applications so
生产就绪的弹簧应用
what did they mean by that opinionated
他们的观点是什么意思
yeah pinion eight they want you to get
是的，小齿轮八，他们希望你得到
up and running what's with spring as
启动并运行spring
fast as possible so in the old days it
尽可能快，所以在过去
could take a while to to get your spring
可能要花一些时间才能得到春天
application up and running you need to
应用程序启动并运行，您需要
write a lot of configuration a lot of
写很多配置很多
XML every time for every project you
每次为您的每个项目使用XML
need to do the same thing and and check
需要做同样的事情，并检查
like what I have to do with this
就像我与此有关
dispatch your servlet again or all that
再次调度您的servlet或所有其他
kind of stuff so spring boot makes that
弹簧靴使
easier for you they have this
他们更容易为您
option of convention over configuration
约定优于配置的选项
so what they mean by that is they
所以他们的意思是
already assume a lot of things for you
已经为你承担了很多事情
so that you don't have to worry about it
这样您就不必担心
and they already take care of many
他们已经照顾了很多
dependencies again so you don't have to
再次依赖，因此您不必
care about it they offer also
关心他们也提供
production-ready features like metrics
可用于生产的功能（例如指标）
health checks and externalized confirm a
健康检查和外部确认
configuration so in the form of
这样配置的形式
endpoints and extra dependencies no more
端点和额外的依赖关系
XML yay that's that's been a while you
是的，XML已经有一段时间了
could already do all your configuration
可以完成所有配置
in Java but now you don't you don't
在Java中，但现在您不这样做了
really have to write a lot anymore
真的必须写很多了
together and like a solid spring app
在一起，就像一个坚实的春季应用程序
running and basically what we're going
运行，基本上我们要去
to talk about today is how the starter
今天要谈的是入门
pumps very simplify your configuration a
泵非常简化您的配置
lot in in maven and we're going to talk
在行家里很多，我们要谈谈
about how it actually works behind the
关于它实际上是如何工作的
scenes first I'm gonna give like a
首先我要给场景
really short example of how fast you can
可以做多快的简短示例
create an app I know that a lot of
创建一个应用程序，我知道很多
people already saw this but just to show
人们已经看到了这个，但只是为了展示
you just go to start that spring that IO
你只是去那个春天开始
or you use the IDE all the IDS provide
或者您使用IDS提供的所有IDE
plug-ins for this exact thing
确切的插件
you go to this you choose your version
你去这个，你选择你的版本
snapshots version you fill in your group
您填写的快照版本
your demo and you say okay I want a web
您的演示，您说好，我想要一个网络
application there you go you got your
你去那里的应用程序，你有你的
application that's out here I'll quickly
这里的应用程序，我很快
scroll down go to my downloads and see
向下滚动到我的下载并查看
the demo now so what show what's in
现在的演示，那么展示什么内容
there so everyone sees so basically
在那里，每个人基本上都看到了
there's a demo application Java class
有一个演示应用程序Java类
there's an application properties
有一个应用程序属性
there's a test class and there's a pump
有一个测试班，有一个泵
file so let's check out the palm file it
文件，所以让我们检查一下手掌文件吧
doesn't contain much can everyone see
含量不高，每个人都能看到
this put a big bigger so it's basic palm
这放了大一点，所以它是基本手掌
the most important part is the parents
最重要的部分是父母
defines the parents the spring boots
定义父母的 spring boot
started parents which take care takes
刚开始照顾父母的父母
care of a lot of the dependencies that
照顾很多依赖
you might add so you don't have to look
您可以添加，所以您不必看
up all the versions of all the different
列出所有不同版本的所有版本
dependencies there's some properties
依赖有一些属性
standard is Java 8 and it includes the
标准是Java 8，它包括
spring boot starter like the the very
春季启动启动器非常
the biggest spring boot started there is
那里开始的最大的 spring boot 是
the spring boot starter core in fact and
实际上，Spring Boot启动器的核心是
it includes the the test dependency
它包括测试依赖项
which we're not gonna use right now it
我们现在不会使用它
also defines the spring boot maven
还定义了 spring boot 专家
plugins so when you when you point a
插件，所以当您指向一个
package your application in jar they
将您的应用程序打包到jar中
take care it take takes care of that so
照顾它要照顾好所以
that's basically it so if you do this if
基本上就是这样，如果您这样做
you install as maven artifacts yeah I
您将其安装为Maven工件，是的，我
haven't been working with the 1.41 a lot
一直没有使用1.41
so nice to download a lot but basically
非常好下载很多，但基本上
it will build your jar and process all
它将建立您的罐子并处理所有
the other dependencies and put all those
其他依赖项，并把所有那些
jars in your jar it's actually a pretty
罐子里的罐子其实很漂亮
neat system if you go look into the
整洁的系统，如果你去看看
source code how it packs all the jars
源代码如何包装所有罐子
very efficiently and then basically you
非常有效，然后基本上
can run the jar
可以运行罐子
I think it's demo right you run it if
我认为这是演示，如果您运行
you have the correct
你有正确的
yeah the web started okay
是的，网络开始正常了
so that's basically same one
所以基本上是一样的
so all the spring boots we're starters
所以所有的 spring boot 我们都开始
start with spring boots starter so if
从弹簧靴起动器开始，所以如果
you're gonna write your own spring boot
你要写自己的 spring boot
starter you know you're not supposed to
初学者，你知道你不应该
you're not supposed to start with spring
你不应该从春天开始
boots starter so it's better to use your
启动靴子，所以最好使用
own name or unique identifier and then
自己的名称或唯一标识符，然后
end with - spring boot starter so if you
结束于-Spring Boot Starter，所以如果您
do like this we install it's it's gonna
像这样，我们将安装它
bring in all the other dependencies
引入所有其他依赖项
there we go we got a working web
到那里，我们有了一个可以正常使用的网络
application so that's really simple but
应用程序，这真的很简单，但是
now everyone of course wants to know how
现在每个人当然都想知道
does this work we go to the presentation
这项工作我们去演讲
so how does this work a lot of people
那么这对很多人如何起作用
that start with spring boots have the
以弹簧靴开始的
have the notion or are a bit frustrated
有这个想法或有点沮丧
that we don't know how this works we're
我们不知道这是如何工作的
losing control how can we influence the
失去控制我们如何影响
configuration etc so there might be a
配置等，所以可能有一个
little frustrated and they might think
有点沮丧，他们可能会认为
what did all how does it work that all
到底是怎么做的
is it magic did all the guys from from
难道所有的家伙都来自
spring go into like pivotal office one
春天进入关键办公室之一
night drank a lot of beer and then
晚上喝了很多啤酒，然后
started writing some code and then the
开始编写一些代码，然后
day after magically they had something
神奇的第二天，他们有了东西
working but I didn't know how well is it
工作，但我不知道效果如何
magic yes
魔术是的
it's magic they actually did this and
他们实际上做到了这是魔术，
they when a new room got drunk they
他们当新房间喝醉了
wrote something and then that came out
写点东西然后出来
well not really that was a lie so so
真的不是那样的谎言
full web had an interesting tweet there
整个网络上有一条有趣的推文
were a lot of complaints about people
很多关于人的抱怨
from people they were saying like the
他们说的人
spring boot stuff is too much magic we
spring boot 的东西太多了，我们
don't know what's going on make it less
不知道发生了什么事使它减少了
magic but like a couple of years ago
魔术，但像几年前
everyone was complaining this this
每个人都在抱怨这个
spring application you have to do so
春季申请，你必须这样做
much configuration it's crazy
如此疯狂的配置
make it less configuration so yeah
减少配置，是的
people need always need to have
人们总是需要拥有
something to complain about that that
对此有所抱怨
tweet was pretty popular back in March
三月份的推文很受欢迎
and it has a good point but don't worry
它有一个好处，但是不用担心
I'll explain everything about the spring
我会解释关于春天的一切
boot starters so let's try to make a
启动启动程序，让我们尝试制作一个
spring boot application and see what
春季启动应用程序，看看
happens it's still a demo so we'll see
碰巧仍然是一个演示，所以我们将看到
here's the business case of the small
这是小企业的案例
application let's get to work so the fre
应用程序，让我们开始工作，这样
P handheld business case has concluded
P掌上商务案例结案
the overall net cost benefit of a
a的整体净成本收益
handheld is unacceptable significantly
手持设备明显不可接受
different from the current not numb
与当前不麻木不同
they're not gonna do that we're not
他们不会那样做，我们不是
gonna do that that's too boring we're
那样做太无聊了
gonna do another business case which is
要做另一个商业案例
more fun we're gonna do a business case
更有趣的是我们要做一个商业案例
called rock-paper-scissors- lizard-spock
叫剪刀石头布蜥蜴麻雀
i know a lot of people have heard
我知道很多人都听过
seniors on Big Bang Theory
大爆炸理论的前辈
like Sheldon he had a cool game it's
像谢尔顿一样，他的比赛很棒
pretty complicated if you if you want to
如果你想的话，这相当复杂
do it good but basically it's scissors
做得很好，但基本上是剪刀
cuts paper paper covers rock rock
剪纸纸盖岩石岩石
crushes lizard lizard poisons Spock
粉碎蜥蜴蜥蜴毒药Spock
Spock smashes scissors scissors
Spock捣碎剪刀
decapitates lizard lizard eats paper
斩首蜥蜴蜥蜴吃纸
paper disproves Spock Spock vaporizes
纸反驳Spock Spock蒸发
rock and as it always has Rock crushes
岩石，因为它总是有岩石碎屑
scissors so I went out and I try to make
剪刀，所以我出去，我尝试做
a starter or a web application which
启动器或Web应用程序
implements this as a game and I had some
将此实现为游戏，我有一些
requirements right so I wanted to be
要求正确，所以我想成为
lightweight I wanted to be stateless
我想成为无国籍的轻量级
because I want a scale it like when my
因为我想要像我
game is really popular everyone in the
游戏真的很受欢迎
world is playing it I want to be
世界在玩，我想成为
stateless I want to be cloud native for
无状态的我想成为云原生
the same reason well stateless is one of
同样的原因，无国籍是其中之一
the the key key things of cloud native
云原生的关键关键事物
and I want to do out the authentication
我想进行身份验证
of was over Twitter so he was spring
的是Twitter，所以他是春天
social and spring security and bring
社会和春季安全并带来
them together but I don't want to use
他们在一起，但我不想使用
JDBC so if any of you know spring social
JDBC，所以如果您认识Spring Social
has like spring social security has two
就像春天的社会保障有两个
implementations to hold the the Twitter
举行Twitter的实现
information like the the Alt key and the
诸如Alt键和
Refresh token stuff like that and I
像这样刷新令牌内容
don't want to get it from Twitter every
不想每次都从Twitter获得它
time so they hold it in like some kind
时间，所以他们把它像某种
of social connection objects and there's
社会联系对象的
basically two implementations and in
基本上有两个实现
memory data implementation and a JDBC
内存数据实现和JDBC
implementation but as I said we don't
实施，但正如我所说，我们没有
want JDBC implementation so I went out
需要JDBC实现，所以我出去了
and I wanted to make a Redis
我想做一个Redis
implementation which is like a
实现就像
distributed cache and you can scale it
分布式缓存，您可以扩展它
horizontally together with your
与您一起水平
application so I also want to make it
应用程序，所以我也想做到
stateless so I'm gonna use spring spring
无状态，所以我要用spring spring
session to store the session also in
会话以将会话也存储在
Redis that's my backup plan so I'm gonna
Redis是我的备份计划，所以我要
show the little starter that I made and
展示我做的小入门
let me see so this is the application
让我看看，这是应用程序
and it has some configuration like
它具有一些配置，例如
security configuration
安全配置
it's pretty pretty regular security
这是非常常规的安全性
except I'm adding the security configure
除了我要添加安全配置
which is a spring social configure and
这是一个春季社交配置，
the spring social configure is coming
春天的社交配置即将到来
from my starter so I'm gonna show the
从我的初学者开始，所以我要展示
starter which is a little bit well not
起动器有点不好
really bigger but I have the the auto
真的更大，但我有自动
configuration I have two but that one is
配置我有两个，但那个是
for later and basically this is how a
稍后，基本上这是
starter can look like so if I open the
初学者看起来像这样，如果我打开
palm you see that I have a lot of
手掌，你看到我有很多
dependencies I have my regular artifact
依赖我有我的常规工件
details personal details get up stuff
详细信息个人详细信息起床的东西
and then I include the spring boot Auto
然后我加入了Spring Boot Auto
configure so this is the one that you
配置，所以这是你
want to include your auto configuration
想要包括您的自动配置
code then you have your dependencies
代码，那么你就有了依赖
that you always gonna need it's not
你永远需要的不是
optional if you if you're going to use
如果您要使用，则为可选
the starter you're gonna need it so
首先你会需要它，所以
there's this thing called spring data
有一个叫做弹簧数据的东西
Redis and especially version 1.7 and up
Redis，尤其是1.7及更高版本
provides Redis repositories where you
提供您在其中的Redis存储库
just use regular repositories like in
只需使用像
data JPA and you can persist them to
数据JPA，您可以将其持久保存到
Redis in the same way as in data GPA so
Redis的方式与数据GPA中的方式相同
I can show an example it's basically you
我可以举一个例子，基本上就是你
have not an entity but a Redis hash you
没有实体，而是Redis哈希
give it a name and then you couldn't
给它起个名字，然后你就不能
have a couple of indexes where you want
在需要的地方有几个索引
to search on and some fields and it will
搜索和一些领域，它将
be stored in Redis like transparently
像透明地存储在Redis中
for you so this is a social radius
对你来说这是一个社交半径
connection repository it's basically the
连接存储库基本上是
same as in data GPA you have a credit
与数据GPA中的相同
repositories and you just provide some
存储库，您只需提供一些
interface methods and spring data Redis
接口方法和spring数据Redis
will take care of the rest
会照顾剩下的
I also contributed this this
我也贡献了这个
implementation to the spring social
实施到春季社会
spring social projects it's an app or
春季社交项目，它是一个应用程序或
requests it still needs some work so I'm
要求它还需要一些工作，所以我
probably going to finish that later this
可能稍后会完成
month I think and then try to get it
我认为一个月，然后尝试得到它
committed in the project so basically if
基本上在项目中投入
you want to do the raddest thing you
你想做最烂的事情
have to implement two in
必须实施两个
faces which is the users connection
面对用户的连接
repository and the connection repository
存储库和连接存储库
which is this one is specifically per
这是每个人专门的
person so it's all the implementation
人，这就是全部实施
details not important more important
细节不重要更重要
this is what you want to talk about is
这就是你想谈的
the other configuration so basically
其他配置基本上
what do what you need to do to get an
您需要做什么才能获得
auto configuration in a starter so
在启动器中自动配置，因此
basically you have to annotate it with
基本上你必须用
add configuration and you have to
添加配置，您必须
mention it or specify it in the spring
在春季提及或指定
dot factories file which is in the meta
元工厂中的点工厂文件
in folder so the key is the enable auto
在文件夹中，所以关键是启用自动
configuration class and then you define
配置类，然后您定义
values one or more values of other
重视另一个的一个或多个价值
configurations that you wish to load
您希望加载的配置
when you load the starter so in your
当您加载启动器时，
regular application if you include the
如果您包括常规申请
starter spring has a spring factories
起动弹簧有弹簧工厂
loader class which looks in the class
在该类中查找的加载程序类
spot at all the meta and folders and
发现所有的meta和文件夹，以及
looks after it searches for spring nut
照顾它寻找弹簧螺母
factories files it checks all these
工厂文件会检查所有这些
files it finds the auto configurations
找到自动配置的文件
and loads them in these other
并将它们加载到其他
configurations are all loaded in in a
配置全部加载到
specific order and you can define this
具体的顺序，您可以定义此
order if you want to load something
如果要加载东西，请订购
before another one or or after it
在另一个之前或之后
so basically spring figured out it
所以基本上春天知道了
figures out the order loads all the auto
找出所有自动加载的订单
configurations as well as this one
配置以及这一
so the second important part are the
所以第二个重要部分是
conditional annotations so this one is a
条件注释，所以这是一个
conditional on class and what it means
以班级为条件及其含义
is this auto configuration will only be
这个自动配置只会
loaded if the Redis connection factory
如果Redis连接工厂已加载
class this one is on the class path so
上课这是在上课的路上
spring boot has a very efficient way of
弹簧靴有一个非常有效的方法
checking this and it will not load the
检查它，它不会加载
configuration this configuration class
配置此配置类
or this other configuration if it's not
或其他配置（如果不是）
on a class path you also have the
在课堂上，你也有
conditional arm beam but they only work
有条件的臂梁，但它们只起作用
on other beans so you can put
在其他豆上，所以你可以放
conditional on bean or kept conditional
有条件的或有条件的
on missing bean you can't put them on on
在缺少的豆子上，你不能把它们放在
configuration classes
配置类
you can also as I said specify an order
您也可以按照我说的指定订单
you can auto configure after an auto
您可以在自动后自动配置
configure before so basically I want to
配置之前，所以基本上我想
configure it before my own Twitter Redis
在我自己的Twitter Redis之前配置它
of the configuration which is the thing
东西的配置
I had to do you can see it's in the
我必须做的是，您可以看到它在
Spring Framework package because
Spring Framework包，因为
basically the the normal Twitter auto
基本上是普通的Twitter自动
configuration always takes the in-memory
配置始终占用内存
implementation and you can't override it
实现，您不能覆盖它
I've been struggling with it for a while
我已经挣扎了一段时间
if anyone can help me the repository is
如果有人可以帮助我，知识库是
online and and you can have a look if
在线，你可以看看
you can fix it I'll give you like more
你可以解决它，我会给你更多
than one beer
比一杯啤酒
so this Twitter Redis other
所以这个Twitter Redis其他
configurations very much like the old
配置非常像旧的
one but I have like some override
一个，但我喜欢一些替代
methods for instance over here the ID
方法，例如ID
source and I'm basically using another
来源，我基本上是用另一个
configuration properties namespace so
配置属性名称空间所以
that's another cool thing configuration
那是另一个很酷的配置
properties our properties that you can
拥有我们可以拥有的财产
define yourself so in spring boot you
定义自己，以便在春季启动时
can use configurations properties in the
可以在
configuration files or in the
配置文件或
application of properties files and you
属性文件的应用程序和您
can define your own and even in the IDE
甚至可以在IDE中定义自己的
s you get really cool autocomplete and
s您会获得非常出色的自动完成功能，
everything so if I were to go to the
一切，所以如果我要去
application properties file I could use
我可以使用的应用程序属性文件
this namespace and add app ID and fill
此名称空间，并添加应用ID和填充
it in or override it whatever so that's
它或覆盖它，所以这是
a really cool feature as well think
一个非常酷的功能以及思考
basically this is the most important one
基本上这是最重要的
so the radius connection Factory is the
所以半径连接工厂是
one that you want to use in your main
您要在主广告中使用的一个
application right so if your main
应用程序正确，所以如果您的主要
application adds the radius connection
应用程序添加了半径连接
factory or adds a working radius
工厂或增加工作半径
connection factory this beam will be
连接工厂，该光束将是
loaded as a primary beam and it will
加载为主光束，它将
generate this radius template and set
生成此半径模板并设置
the radius connection factory so if you
半径连接工厂，如果您
don't have a radius connection factory
没有半径连接工厂
in your main application this will never
在您的主应用程序中，这永远不会
get loaded this one is not that it's an
被加载这不是不是它是一个
implementation detail so not that
实现细节，所以不是
important so
重要的是
ready to like show the application so I
准备好喜欢显示应用程序，所以我
told you the security configure is the
告诉你安全配置是
one that I configured in the Twitter
我在Twitter中配置的一个
Auto configuration class so it will find
自动配置类，因此它将找到
the beam on the class spot and use this
在课场上使用光束
one I have a social configuration which
我有一种社会结构
is basically how I want to sign in and
基本上就是我要登录的方式
it has the connection factory so it's
它有连接工厂，所以
the the Jadis client implementation that
Jadis客户端实现
I'm using and I mean going for local
我正在使用，我的意思是去当地
hosts on on a darker radius image so
托管在半径更暗的图像上，因此
darker is running a Redis locally and
较暗的是在本地运行Redis
he'll connect to death this is the
他将连接到死亡，这是
WebSocket configuration which is
WebSocket配置是
basically for the game to have a couple
基本上是为了让游戏有一对
of endpoints I can send chat messages
我可以发送聊天消息的端点
and I can send game game messages the
我可以发送游戏信息
controller not really that important you
控制器不是那么重要
have like two basic endpoints for for my
对于我来说有两个基本端点
templates my time leave templates and
模板，我的时间离开模板，
then you have the game endpoints for the
那么您就拥有了
chat and events and you have a player
聊天和事件，你有一个球员
endpoint to check out your currents well
端点检查好你的电流
your own information to get your own
您自己的信息以获得自己的信息
information
信息
this one also for authentication
这个也用于身份验证
purposes so it's basically spring social
目的，所以基本上是春季社交
security and you have some chat messages
安全性，您有一些聊天消息
game events game messages and a player a
游戏事件游戏消息和玩家a
player object but the main application
播放器对象，但主要应用
basically is still just a spring booth
基本上还是春天的摊位
application the spring booth application
春季展位申请
is an annotation and it contains this
是一个注释，它包含此
very important one the at enable are the
非常重要的一点是
configuration so this is the one that
配置，所以这是那个
starts off the entire other
从另一个开始
configuration life cycle or whatever you
配置生命周期或其他
want to call it and it does the ordering
想调用它并执行排序
it checks all the beans it checks all
它检查所有的豆子它检查所有的豆子
the conditions and if you have the
条件，如果你有
actuator dependency it will also make
致动器的依赖性也会使
the actuator endpoints like Auto config
执行器端点，例如自动配置
and the slash beans so if you want to
和斜线豆，所以如果你想
check out the application I'll just run
签出我将要运行的应用程序
it here
在这里
all right
好吧
so this is basically rock-paper-scissors
所以这基本上是剪刀石头布
lizard-spock as explanations on how to
蜥蜴-spock作为有关如何
play and you can log in through Twitter
播放，您可以通过Twitter登录
so it go to Twitter authenticate
所以它去Twitter认证
yourself and then come back it's
自己，然后回来
basically the same page and then it
基本相同的页面，然后
knows you're authenticated and it will
知道您已通过身份验证，它将
add some more you have a chat that goes
再加上一些您可以进行的聊天
over WebSockets
通过WebSockets
and then if I say hello you can see that
然后，如果我打招呼，你可以看到
it's sending a overstock GS and stomp
它发送了积压的GS和重踩
it's sending messages back and forth so
它来回发送消息，所以
if I have to - if I create a new window
如果需要-如果创建一个新窗口
I log in I have to follow my credentials
我登录必须遵循我的凭据
the only annoying thing is that it's me
唯一讨厌的是我
and me so this is me and this is me so
和我，这就是我，这就是我，所以
if I say hello here sends a WebSocket
如果我打招呼这里发送一个WebSocket
message and then it gets sent out to the
消息，然后将其发送到
topics and to the other one so if I want
主题和另一个主题，如果我想
to join I click here it gets it fetches
加入我点击这里获取它
my player information gets my Twitter
我的玩家信息获取我的Twitter
your image and then it fills in my
您的图像，然后填充我的
twitter handle same here
Twitter在这里处理相同
the problem is I'm player - it checks if
问题是我是玩家-它会检查
player one is not the same as me so I
玩家一与我不同，所以我
can't play as player two as well so the
不能同时作为第二人玩
problem is I wanted to show you this to
问题是我想向您展示
you guys on the fly and I wanted to
你们在飞行中，我想
deploy it to PCF and I did so if you
部署到PCF，如果您这样做的话
want to go to PCF I think it's somewhere
我想去PCF
over here yeah so it's running
在这边，它正在运行
rock-paper-scissors- lizard-spock dot c
石头剪刀布蜥蜴麻点c
FF z io it's running on P dubs and as
FF z io正在P配音上运行
you can see I'm having problems with the
您可以看到我在使用
WebSockets I've saw some issues about it
WebSockets我已经看到了一些问题
I don't really know how to fix it in
我真的不知道如何解决它
this short notice I only saw it at the
这个短暂的通知我只在
end when I deployed so that was a bit
我部署时结束，所以有点
bad on my part but basically when I
对我来说不好，但基本上当我
login comes back and then it gives me
登录回来，然后它给了我
the WebSocket error so I wanted to show
WebSocket错误，所以我想显示
you guys I deployed it and I wanted to
你们我部署了它，我想
play with you guys during the
在比赛中与你们一起玩
presentation but yeah it's been not
演示文稿，但不是
going to be work so if anyone can help
会上班的，所以如果有人可以帮忙
me with that much appreciate it so if we
非常感谢我，所以如果我们
can't play
不能玩
this we need to have another game right
这我们需要另一场比赛
so I'm going back to the presentation
所以我要回到演讲中
and I'm gonna wait put this thing here
我要等这东西放在这里
so that was the business case this is my
这就是商业案例，这是我的
backup plan
后备方案
Josh long is always my back-up plan so
乔希（Josh Long）永远是我的后援计划，所以
everyone knows Josh along the spring
大家都知道乔什在春天
like spring guru goes all over the world
就像春天的大师遍布世界
to talk to to so many people and then
与很多人交谈，然后
give much talks and wear down his own
进行大量的演讲，自己做文章
voice and we're gonna play Josh long
声音，我们要扮演乔希
Pokemon so Josh long has this game on
宠物小精灵，所以乔什（Josh）很久以前就玩这款游戏
Twitter he's during the conference he's
他在会议期间的Twitter
meeting everyone and he's trying to get
与所有人见面，他正在努力
a selfie with all the very important
与所有非常重要的自拍照
people of spring and pivotal so I
春天和关键的人，所以我
basically want to make a starter which
基本上想做一个入门
provides by default an endpoint where
默认提供一个端点，其中
you can get random Josh long pics josh
你可以得到随机的乔什长照片乔什
trank Pokemon so it's a spring boot
转动神奇宝贝，所以这是一个弹簧靴
starter it needs to provide an endpoints
首先，它需要提供一个端点
to retrieve Josh Long's Pokemon and I
检索乔希·朗的口袋妖怪和我
want to make it somewhat configurable so
想要使其可配置，以便
that's much simpler than the other one
这比另一个简单得多
so I'll show you the code where's this
所以我会告诉你代码在哪里
one with all these windows so this is
所有这些窗户一个，所以这是
the other configuration this is the
其他配置是
starter so basically I have some random
入门，所以基本上我有一些随机
Twitter pics from yesterday I call them
昨天的Twitter图片我称它们为
the wild Pokemon and the most important
野生的神奇宝贝和最重要的
thing again is the ad configuration and
再次是广告配置和
as I said also the spring-locks
我也说弹簧锁
factory's file so every time same thing
工厂的文件，所以每次都一样
this will get loaded automatically and
这将自动加载，
he'll find the auto configuration class
他会找到自动配置类
what I'm doing is I'm doing another
我在做另一件事
component scan because it's easier and
组件扫描，因为它更容易并且
I'm lazy and it will find this Josh long
我很懒，它将发现这个乔希
pics controller and this is also a cool
图片控制器，这也很酷
one you have conditional on class
你有条件的一个
conditional on being missing being
以失踪为条件
missing class conditional on property
以财产为条件的缺课
but you also have conditional on web
但是你也有条件上网
application and that's a pretty big one
应用程序，这是一个很大的应用程序
it's basically condition and they made a
这基本上是条件，他们做了
spring booth team made a
春季展位团队做了
and like a very short cuts condition
就像捷径一样
class spring boot condition which you
你的上课春季启动条件
can extend and basically it has a lot of
可以扩展，基本上它有很多
stuff to check if you have a web
检查您是否有网站的东西
application I haven't looked into it too
我也没有研究过的应用程序
much so what our and auto-configuration
以及我们的自动配置
does is it has the random pictures you
是不是有随机图片
can get this from a database or whatever
可以从数据库中获取
or from a web source and I have a couple
或通过网络来源，我有几个
of beans you can see that they all
豆，您可以看到它们全部
return the same beam or the same beam
返回相同的光束或相同的光束
class so you're thinking I'm gonna have
上课，所以你以为我会
a conflict or something he is gonna have
冲突或他将要发生的事情
if you want other Y or just beam in your
如果您想要其他Y或只是在
main application he's not gonna find the
他不会找到的主要应用
the correct one but basically they all
正确的，但基本上都是
have different kinds of annotations
有不同种类的注释
conditional on missing beam is just
以缺少光束为条件
saying that if I'm if you don't have a
说，如果我没有你
picture provider take this one and
图片提供商拿这个
conditional on property checks for a
以财产检查为条件
property called Josh dot long job dot
称为Josh点的长期作业点
pics having the value random so if the
图片具有随机值，因此如果
the property has that value it will
该属性具有该值，它将
basically return a random pick provider
基本上返回一个随机选择提供者
and it's basically doing a random and
基本上是随机的
going over the lists and giving you a
查看列表并给您一个
random image the next one is also
随机图片下一个也是
conditional a missing beam and
有条件的缺少光束
conditional on property pics orders so
以财产图片订单为条件
this is giving you ordered pick provider
这给您订购的接送服务商
and you can go on and go on and make
然后你可以继续做下去
your starter very configurable this way
您的启动器可以通过这种方式进行配置
you can also make your own conditions as
您也可以根据自己的条件
I showed in the conditional on web
我在网络上显示了条件
application basically you implement the
应用程序基本上是您实现
condition class or you extend the very
条件类或您扩展非常
easy spring boot condition class which
简易弹簧启动条件类
has a lot of shorthand methods and by
有很多速记方法
default without a property if the
默认不带属性，如果
property does not exist I'm gonna pick
属性不存在，我要选择
the ordered pick provider as well so
订购的选择提供者也是如此
this is basically very simple it takes
这基本上很简单
the pics copies them orders them and
图片复制他们命令他们，
returns them and then every time it just
返回它们，然后每次
goes over the next one so that's my
翻到下一个，那是我的
starter I don't have any application
入门我没有任何应用程序
properties in my starter you could add
您可以在我的入门中添加属性
some defaults but usually you want to do
一些默认值，但通常您想这样做
the properties on the on your
上的属性
application side
应用方
which uses the the starter and I've
使用入门，我已经
already run it I think I can run it
已经运行了，我想我可以运行了
again there we go little success and
再次，我们没有成功，
then this is the application it's really
然后这是真正的应用程序
small again it's bring good application
再小的它带来了很好的应用
and basically I have an index file with
基本上我有一个索引文件
jQuery and my custom JavaScript it goes
jQuery和我的自定义JavaScript
to the Josh long endpoints which I
到我的Josh长端点
created here I didn't show this one yet
在这里创建，我还没有显示
the Josh long endpoint just gets the
乔什长终点只是得到
picture provided switch is auto wired at
图片提供的开关在
runtime and it gets the next picture so
运行时，它将获取下一张图片，因此
it gets to the URL of the picture and on
它到达图片的URL
this one I retrieve one of the Josh
这个我找一个乔希
Flaum Pokemon pictures I log it and I
Flaum Pokemon图片我记录下来，我
set the attribute of the source so
设置源的属性，以便
that's a little my best JavaScript
那是我最好的JavaScript
you're ever gonna see so let's run it I
你永远会看到的，所以让我们运行它
think it's gonna fail because the other
认为这会失败，因为另一个
one is running but I want to show that
一个正在运行，但我想表明
as well
以及
I think Stephan Nicole also showed it
我认为斯蒂芬·妮可（Stephan Nicole）也展示了它
already so this is such a life saver and
因此，这就是这样的救生器，
time-saver
省时间
you always find what's what's wrong but
你总会发现出什么问题了，但是
this one saves time and you immediately
这节省了时间，您立即
know okay this other application is
知道这个其他应用程序是
still running shut it down so that's a
仍在运行关闭它，所以这是一个
really cool feature from spring boot 1.4
Spring Boot 1.4的真正酷功能
so my application started and you can
所以我的应用程序启动了，你可以
see that it mapped the Josh long pics
看到它映射了乔希（Josh）的长照片
controller so I didn't have to do
控制器，所以我不必做
anything for that except add the
除了添加任何东西
dependency of the starter so it's really
入门者的依赖性，所以它真的
a very simple process not many magic
一个非常简单的过程，魔术并不多
going on you just have to know how it
继续，你只需要知道它如何
works and I have some application
工作，我有一些应用
properties which is Josh Lang picks
Josh Lang选择的房地产
random so if I go to the application my
随机的，所以如果我去申请
very very cool application Josh long
非常非常酷的应用程序Josh Long
Pokemon gotta catch em all so if you
口袋妖怪一定要抓住它们
refresh so now it's in random modes it
刷新，所以现在它处于随机模式
has the random
有随机
so you could probably get twice the same
所以你可能会得到两倍
picture I saw there twice the same
我在那看过两次一样的照片
picture in a row
连续图片
shaggy elmer here we went out last night
毛茸茸的埃尔默，我们昨晚出去了
he's a very cool guy you should talk to
他是一个很酷的人，你应该和他聊天
him and that's about it so I just if I
他，就是这样，所以我就好像我
change the property or use like the
更改属性或使用像
spring Netflix cloud config server and I
春天的Netflix云配置服务器和我
can change the properties on the fly but
可以随时更改属性，但
I'll do it like this for the moments
我现在就这样做
probably after restart
可能在重启后
so now it should go nicely in order and
所以现在它应该可以顺畅地运行了，
not show any it's hard to see because
没有显示任何很难看到的，因为
they're not numbered or anything but
他们没有编号或其他任何东西
just to show you you have as I said you
只是为了告诉你你有我所说的
had our token fig oh wait my plugin is
让我们的令牌无花果哦，等等我的插件是
not loading in the there we go so when
没有加载在那里，我们去，所以当
you go to the other config endpoint
你去另一个配置端点
which is enabled by the spring boot
通过Spring Boot启用
actuator you can see the positive
执行器可以看到正面
matches it found and a negative matches
与找到的匹配项和否定匹配项
so usually not you're less interested in
所以通常你对它不感兴趣
a negative matches but you want to see
否定的比赛，但您想看看
the positive ones and you can search for
积极的，你可以搜索
Josh long as you can see here Josh long
乔什（Josh），只要您在这里可以看到
josh long Iman that's how I called it
乔什·伊曼（Joseph Long Iman）就是这样
initially other configuration and it
最初是其他配置，
finds the Josh long amount other
找到乔希长的其他
configuration ordered Josh long pick
配置命令Josh Long Pick
provider so in the properties it was
提供者，因此在属性中
ordered so it's going to give you that
下令，它会给你
beam and it shows you the condition it
光束，它告诉你状况
was an ambient condition and conditioner
是环境条件和护发素
are missing beam and that's about it if
缺少光束，就是这样
you check out the negative matches you
您查看否定匹配项
see the other one the defaults and a
看到另一个默认值和一个
randomized so those are negative matches
随机，所以那些是负匹配
it's always handy to see this and you
看到这个总是很方便
see why it's it didn't load so it
看看为什么它没有加载所以
expected to random property for
预期具有随机属性
properties Josh long optics so that's
属性乔希长光学，所以
really handy to check out why isn't the
非常方便查看为什么不是
starter working as I thought it did
入门者按照我的想法工作
doubt it should and what I have to do to
怀疑它应该和我该怎么做
change it remove this
改变它删除这个
so this was pretty basic
所以这很基本
that was my backup plane plan let's
那是我的备用飞机计划，让我们
recap very quickly the other
很快回顾另一个
configuration is not magic as you saw
如您所见，配置并不是魔术
you can explain everything that's
你可以解释一切
happening and the pivotal guys didn't go
发生了，关键人物没有去
in a room and get drunk
在房间里喝醉
maybe they did but they didn't right
也许他们做到了，但他们做错了
spring boots during and so the first
春季靴，所以第一个
thing is spring boot application enables
事情是 spring boot 应用程序启用
the other configuration with the
其他配置
annotation the spring factory's loader
注释弹簧工厂的装载机
removes the need for class but scanning
无需上课，但可以扫描
because that can be take a while right
因为那可能需要一段时间
if you have a big class spots you just
如果你有一个大班级的景点，你只是
want to go to the Auto configuration
想要进入自动配置
creation Auto configuration class and it
创建自动配置类及其
will it will only do the things that you
它只会做你的事情吗
want to do it won't scan the entire
想要这样做不会扫描整个
class but conditional on class and beam
阶级，但以阶级和梁为条件
or on missing class and missing beam are
或缺少班级和缺少梁
really handy to make your spring boot
使您的春季靴真的很方便
starter configurable the naming thing is
初学者可配置的命名是
I mentioned that do not start with
我说过不要以
spring boots starter even if you think
弹簧靴启动器，即使您认为
it's going to be it's going to be
这将会是
adopted right away by the spring team
被春季团队立即采用
and they really want to keep this this
他们真的想保留这个
namespace for them for future references
它们的命名空间，以供将来参考
so you can just add Josh long amount -
这样您就可以长时间添加Josh-
spring boot starter another important
春季启动启动器的另一个重要方面
thing that you might not see in the
您可能看不到的东西
beginning and which might baffle you a
开始，这可能会让您困惑
bit the other configurations all are all
其他配置都全部
executed after the normal application
正常申请后执行
context is loaded so if you're wondering
上下文已加载，因此如果您想知道
why is this been getting loaded and why
为什么要加载它，为什么
is this being not getting loaded this is
这是没有被加载这是
probably the reason and you can also
可能是原因，您也可以
order the different kinds of other
订购不同种类的其他
configurations as I say here Auto
正如我在这里所说的配置自动
configure before and after really handy
配置之前和之后真的很方便
to make sure that some beans are already
确保已经有一些豆子
configured before others you can have
在其他人之前可以配置
the Auto config endpoints the actuator
自动配置会终结执行器
endpoints but you can also do it with
端点，但您也可以使用
debug modes so in most IDs you can do
调试模式，因此在大多数ID中您都可以执行
like enable debug or you can just give
例如启用调试，或者您可以给
the dash dash debug parameter at startup
启动时的破折号调试参数
and the actuator I told you already
我已经告诉过你的执行器
so I think I'm gonna end pretty quickly
所以我想我很快就会结束
because of the the not playing of games
因为不玩游戏
that we did but if you have any
我们所做的，但是如果您有任何
questions I'll be willing to answer them
我愿意回答的问题
yeah
是的
all right so the question was if you
好的，所以问题是你是否
want to combine different kinds of
想要结合不同种类的
dependencies or starters or
依赖项或启动器或
configurations how do you do that well
配置你如何做得好
basically you would just create
基本上你只会创建
different kinds of Auto configs like
不同类型的自动配置，例如
with at configuration class make
与at配置类make
different kinds of classes add your
不同种类的课程会增加您的
dependencies as optional if you can
如果可以的话，依赖项是可选的
because you don't want to load them
因为你不想加载它们
together with your main application if
与您的主要应用程序一起使用
you're not going to use it or if it's
您不打算使用它，或者如果它是
not going to be enabled so you don't
不会启用，所以你不会
want those on a class spot but you can
想要那些在课堂上的人，但是你可以
basically make different kind of Auto
基本上制造不同种类的汽车
configs and add them all to the spring
配置并将其全部添加到春季
that factories file so it will load them
该工厂文件，以便将其加载
in the correct order yes
以正确的顺序是
okay the question is what do you need
好吧，问题是你需要什么
for what you do with versioning of your
对于您的版本控制
starters basically as you version it
入门版，基本上是您的版本
like any other spring like any other
像其他任何春天一样
maven dependency you can use your own
你可以使用自己的Maven依赖
versioning the only thing you have to do
版本控制，您唯一要做的就是
in your main application where you pull
在您的主应用程序中
in the dependency you have to just
在依赖中，你只需要
specify the correct version so it
指定正确的版本，这样
doesn't have to be the same but of
不必相同，但是
course in the starter you're gonna use
您将要使用的入门课程
some kind of version of spring so maybe
春天的某种版本，所以也许
you could use properties files or make
您可以使用属性文件或
sure they are aligned because if you use
确保它们对齐，因为如果您使用
in your starter for example the one that
以您的入门者为例
we got six and then in your main
我们有六个，然后在您的主要
application you're using spring 1.4 it
您正在使用spring 1.4的应用程序
might break have some breaking changes
可能会有所改变
between them and it might break the
他们之间，这可能会破坏
application so the version of the
应用程序的版本
starter itself is not important the
入门者本身并不重要
version of the spring boot dependency
Spring Boot依赖版本
should be as much the same as you can it
应该尽可能地相同
doesn't have to be strictly the same
不必严格相同
version yes
版本是
well the easiest way is in the spring
最简单的方法是在春季
documentation it's explained very well
文档，解释得很好
usually in the documentation they also
通常在文档中
explain how you should package them a
解释如何包装它们
bit usually they advise you to make the
通常，他们建议您使
author configure dependency and the the
作者配置依赖项和
the other one is the like basically to
另一个基本上就像
maven artifacts you have the auto
您拥有自动的Maven工件
configure artifact and then the artifact
配置工件，然后配置工件
which pulls in all the dependencies so
从而拉入所有依赖项
the auto configure one is with only one
自动配置只有一个
dependency and you have the spring boots
依赖，你有 spring boot
Auto configure dependency and there you
自动配置依赖关系
can put all then you have all the the
可以放所有然后你拥有所有
annotations to make your configuration
注释以进行配置
and the auto loading stuff and in the
和自动加载的东西，并在
second one you just list up all your
第二个，你只列出你所有的
optional dependencies so but you can put
可选的依赖项，所以您可以放
them in one artifact like I did they say
像我说的那样，把它们放在一个人工制品中
you can do boats yeah does that answer
你可以做船是的答案
your question question yes
您的问题问题是
so if I understand correctly how do i
所以如果我正确理解我该怎么办
add to servlet filters with different
添加到具有不同的servlet过滤器
names maybe or I think you should use
也许是名字，或者我认为您应该使用
the regular spring setup like use
常规的弹簧设置，如使用
different qualifiers and you can make
不同的预选赛，你可以
them conditional you can make them both
他们有条件，你可以让他们两个
conditional or you can play around with
有条件的，或者你可以玩
the configuration right but basically if
配置权，但基本上如果
you have two beams of the same class or
你有两个相同等级的光束
the same type you would do it like in
您将在其中使用的相同类型
any other spring configuration you would
其他任何弹簧配置
use qualifiers and when you ought to
使用限定词以及何时应该
wire them in your main application you
将它们连接到您的主应用程序中
also use those qualifiers you have to
也要使用那些预选赛
know a bit about the starter then but
然后对启动器有所了解
yeah yes you want to know more about
是的，您想了解更多有关
that all right
没关系
I'll show you so it's it's really pretty
我会告诉你，那真的很漂亮
easy I didn't show the properties that's
容易，我没有显示的属性
correct so basically I'll show it in
正确，所以基本上我会显示
this one for example the Twitter Auto
例如Twitter Auto
configuration has Twitter radius
配置具有Twitter半径
properties file which is a regular class
属性文件是常规类
and you just annotate it with at help
而您只是在帮助下对其进行注释
make it bigger for you you can just add
使它变得更大，您可以添加
it with annotate it with at
用注释
configuration properties and you give it
配置属性，您给它
a namespace and then all the properties
命名空间，然后是所有属性
that are in the in a properties file are
属性文件中的
our author completable in the properties
我们的作者可以在属性中完成
files so if I go up here you have a
文件，所以如果我上这里，你有一个
conditional on a property and then the
有条件的，然后
property is spring that social so I will
财产是社会的春天，所以我会
check it out and and but basically the
检查出来，但基本上
ide all offer supports for they scan the
提供所有提供支持的服务，因为他们扫描了
class path and they process the the
类路径，他们处理
annotations and they give you a lot of
注释，它们给您很多
completion anything else
完成其他任何事情
yeah
是的
yeah so the the all the spring boots
是的，所以所有的 spring boot
starter all the different kind of spring
起动器各种不同的弹簧
wood starters that spring offers and
春天提供的木启动器和
that they oughta configure automatically
他们应该自动配置
in any spring boot application I'll show
在任何春季启动应用程序中，我将展示
you in a minute all these ones have the
您一分钟内所有这些都有
same naming conventions they have spring
他们有春天相同的命名约定
boots starter web spring wood starter
靴子起动器网弹簧木起动器
data GPA and that's why they want to
数据GPA，这就是为什么他们想要
avoid that you use the same namespace so
避免使用相同的名称空间
you can you can use your starter
你可以用你的初学者
anything you want but to make it clear
任何您想要的但要弄清楚
that it's a starter you could just add
这是一个入门，您可以添加
at the end spring boot started that's a
在最后的春季启动开始是
bit the the common
共同点
yeah convention
是的约定
yeah of course yeah just it's a
是的，当然是
convention that you can play with it but
可以玩的约定，但是
you can add stuff like that if you want
您可以根据需要添加类似的内容
yeah no problem just don't use their
是的，没问题就是不要用他们的
namespace you like have a warning about
您喜欢的名称空间有警告
it I'll maybe show the spring boots
我也许会给我看 spring boot
it already has it's pretty big file
它已经有很大的文件了
can't really miss it so this is an
真的不能错过，所以这是
example of the spring boots spring boot
spring boot  spring boot 的例子
auto-configure starter so this also has
自动配置启动器，所以它也有
a spring that factories file and it also
工厂归档的春天
has the enable auto configuration key in
具有启用自动配置密钥
the file and basically it's lists all
该文件，基本上它列出了所有
the different kinds of spring boot
不同种类的弹簧靴
starters that are out there so it
在那里的起动器，所以它
doesn't necessarily load in those
不一定加载那些
configurations but it goes to all these
配置，但所有这些
configuration classes and checks the
配置类并检查
conditions so basically the ALP are the
因此，基本上，ALP是
configuration this class will get loaded
该类的配置将被加载
and I'm not sure how they do it that you
我不确定他们是怎么做到的
don't get runtime exceptions here
不要在这里获得运行时异常
because these classes don't need to be
因为这些课程不需要
on the class spot but they found a way
在课堂上，但他们找到了一种方法
to do that but it basically loads checks
这样做，但它基本上会加载检查
this configuration class I think it's a
我认为这是一个配置类
reflection so it doesn't actually have
反思，所以它实际上没有
to load the class but this will not be
加载类，但这不会
loaded if you don't have anything
如果你什么都没有的话
aspectj related on your class paths so
Aspectj与您的课程路径相关，因此
this is a really quick process and it
这是一个非常快速的过程，
goes over all these other configuration
遍历所有其他配置
classes quickly if you don't use any of
如果您不使用任何
them only the web it will only load that
他们只有网络，它只会加载
one that's how how they do it so I think
他们就是如何做到的，所以我认为
it's a pretty annoying job to keep this
保持这一点很烦人
up to date for for the guys from spring
从春季开始为男孩们最新
boots but they do all the heavy lifting
靴子，但他们都做得很重
for us and we can we can use it any more
对我们来说，我们可以再使用它了
questions yeah
是的
it's better to create the question was
最好提出一个问题是
if you want to override some of the
如果您想覆盖某些
spring boot Auto configurations right it
spring boot自动配置吧
would be better to create your own
更好地创建自己的
starter and load it before the other one
启动器，然后先加载它
so the other one will get loaded but if
所以另一个会被加载，但是如果
you go into one of the for example this
你进入其中一个例如
one that's a bad example nope
那是一个不好的榜样
yeah for example this one if you want to
是的，例如，如果您想
override this one you make your own Auto
覆盖此选项，您将自己制作为自动
configuration you define the same kind
您定义相同类型的配置
of beam and you make sure that it runs
光束，并确保其运行
before this one so you make sure that it
在此之前，请确保
runs at Auto configure before the J some
运行在自动配置之前
other configuration class that's
其他配置类
basically how you would do it and this
基本上你会怎么做，这
one will not load them because it's only
一个不会加载它们，因为它只是
loads when it's missing so this class
缺少时加载，因此此类
will not get loaded so that's how you
不会被加载，所以这就是你
would do it you wouldn't you wouldn't go
会做到的，你不会，你不会去的
into their code or you wouldn't have to
到他们的代码中，否则您不必
do that you can just make your own
那样你就可以自己做
starter and override it does that answer
起动器并覆盖它会回答
a question a bit all right
一个问题还可以
so I think we're good to go there are no
所以我认为我们很好，那里没有
more questions I invite you to take take
我邀请您参加更多问题
a look at the repository if you can fix
看一下存储库是否可以修复
the websocket problem I'm gonna have to
我将不得不解决的websocket问题
look with with the Rosen and another guy
与罗森和另一个人一起看
from that team to fix my problem but
从那个团队来解决我的问题，但是
yeah go out it and try to create your
是的，出去尝试创建您的
own spring good starter there's a lot of
自己的春天很好的入门者，有很多
examples on get up and and it's really
起来的例子，这真的
powerful thank you
厉害，谢谢
you
您